Guide to the Records of the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland 1895-2021 MS 3034
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Governance, 1895-2018
  - Subseries I.D. Officers' files, 1919-2018 (bulk, 1992-2018)
    - Officers' files | Elbrun Kimmelman: Files Including Various Project Notes By Project (40 folders), 2015-2018, undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1-40)
      Topics include: Application forms and various templates; Shop 50 Regalia; Recordkeeping; Digitization archives; Financials and investments -- Reimbursements, Liability and Investment Committee; Dutch language lessons; Program Committee; Activities -- Mary Park's suggestions; Metadata Assistant's Grant to New Netherland Institute; DHD Social Register Article; DHD Travel Guide, "Exploring Historic Dutch New York"; Dutch Research Guide, "Research Your Dutch Ancestors, a Practical Guide"; Knickerbocker Toast; Tulips and Cocktains (Mary 2011); St. Mark's Funding Request (2011); Great Barrington; Gift agreement between DHD and New-York Historical Society for Govert Loockermans deed; Event at New-York Historical Society for donation of Govert Loockermans deed; Grant report including grant to Mr. Artyom Anikin for Translation of COLVE Papers and gift to Netherlands Institute to complete digitization of 17th-century documents in New York Archives and 3-year webpage grant; DHD plaque at Pearl Street; Second Avenue Church Plaque; Restoration of Peter Stuyvesant Window, St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery; St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery iron gate project; Peter Stuyvesant TV program; DHD potential projects; "A Bit of Dutch Thanksgiving" message; Elbrun Kimmelman trip to Leiden as special guest; Anniversary Book; "A Dutch Republic" by Jonathan Israel; Related societies; New Amsterdam History Center; New Netherland Institute; Lafayett's Hermione (2011).
    - Officers' files | Elbrun Kimmelman: Photographs, 2007-2018 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1-10)
      Photographic prints and some CDs of DHD functions, such as annual meetings, Paas Heritage Balls, fieldtrips, and the unveiling of stained glass windows restored by the DHD at St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery (2009) and the New-York Historical Society (2011).
    - Lists of officers, 1919-1994 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
    - Officers' responsibilities, undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
      Descriptions of duties of Recording Secretary, Corresponding Secretary, and Registrar.
- Series II. Subject Files, 1892-2013
  Series II is organized in four subseries:
  Subseries II.A. Meetings, luncheons, receptions, 1900-2013
  Subseries II.B. Projects and general topics, 1896-2013
  Subseries II.C. Talks & papers delivered before the Society & elsewhere, 1892-2013
  Subseries II.D. Artifacts, circa 1898-1990s
  This series pulls together varied documents that were stored in loose files and binders. They include correspondence, ephemera, some photographs, clippings, and general subject files relating to Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland activities, events, interests, projects, and outings. A small collection of artifacts--largely medals depicting Queen Wilhelmina of the Netherlands--rounds out the series.
  - Subseries II.A. Meetings, luncheons, receptions, 1900-2013
    - DHD events, 1900-1945 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
    - DHD events | Henry Hudson 350th Anniversary Luncheon, 1959 March 21 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
    - DHD events | Anniversary Luncheons, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
      For photographs of the 75th Anniversary Luncheon, see box 9, folder 15.
    - DHD events | Dutch Consulate receptions, 2001-2004 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
    - DHD events | St. Nicholas Reception at the New York Genealogical and Biographical Society, 2005 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
    - DHD events | Paas Heritage Ball, 2013 March 15 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices [white binder], 1910-1966 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices [white binder], 1967-1980 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, 1923-1949 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
    - DHD events | Invitations, meeting notices, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
    - DHD stationery, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
    - Non-DHD | Invitations, programs, 1966-1990 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
    - Non-DHD | Invitations, programs, 1991-1995, undated (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
  - Subseries II.B. Projects and general topics, 1896-2013
    - Albany, New York | Schuyler Mansion clock presented by DHD, 1921 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
    - Alden family article, undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 9)
    - American Numismatic Society | DHD insignia presented to, 1909 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 10)
    - Battery Park | Netherlands Memorial, 2000 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 11)
    - Battery Park | Proposed memorial to "ancestors," with litigation, 1913-1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bethell, Union Noble (1859-1933) | published biography (Offsite-box 8, Folder 13)
    - Boer Home Industries, 1906-1908 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 14)
    - Boston | Committee of Correspondence, facsimile of founding document, 1772, circa 1900s (Offsite-box 8, Folder 15)
    - Brinckerhoff Cemetery, Queens, New York, 2000 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Museum | Dutch period room, 1933 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 17)
    - John Carter Brown Library, 1998 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 18)
    - Clippings | DHD, 1897-2012 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 19)
    - Clippings | non-DHD, 1922-2011 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 20)
    - Dutch royal family | photographs, Queen Wilhelmina & Princess Juliana, 1898, 1914 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 21)
    - Dutch royal family | photographs, Queen Juliana, 1952 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
    - Dutch royal family | photographs, Princess Beatrix (2 folders), 1959 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - Dutch royal family | Queen Wilhelmina's membership certificate, Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland, 1896 January 18 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 22)
    - Dutch royal family | Correspondence, 1898-1945 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 23)
    - Dutch royal family | Menu, dinner for Princess Juliana, Waldorf-Astoria, 1944 January 10 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 24-a)
    - Dutch royal family | Commemorative book, The American Visit of the Netherlands Royal Couple, 1952 April 2-28 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 24-b)
    - Dutch royal family | Menu & seating plan, dinner, Waldorf-Astoria, 1952 April 7 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 25)
    - Dutch royal family | Miscellaneous, 1953-1966 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 26-a)
    - Dutch royal family | Princess Beatrix visit, 1959 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 26-b)
    - Dutch royal family | Marriage of Princess Beatrix, press packet, 1966 March 10 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 27)
    - Dutch royal family | Marriage of Princess Beatrix, souvenir issue of Paris Match, no. 884, 1966 March 19 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
    - Dutch royal family | Menu and seating list, Holland Society dinner for Prince Bernhard, The Biltmore, 1967 September 25 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 28)
    - Dutch royal family | Hague Philharmonic at Carnegie Hall, 1969 January 28 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 29)
    - Dutch royal family | American visit, 1982 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 30)
    - Fabend, Firth | New Netherland in a Nutshell, 2012 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 31)
    - Five Dutch Days, 2007-2012 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 32)
      Annual celebration of Dutch arts and culture in New York City (5dutchdaysnyc.org).
    - Flag Day, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 33)
    - Flag of the United States | proper display and respect, 1935-1960 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 34)
    - Fort Sumter flagstaff and tablet dedication program, 1931 April 11 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 35)
    - General Court of Patriotic Societies of America, [1938] (Offsite-box 8, Folder 36)
    - Governors Island | Proposed recreation of Historic New Amsterdam, 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 37)
    - Gross, Geoffrey | Early American Dutch Architecture [book project], 2002 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 38)
    - Grotius Memorial Window, Nieuwe Kerk, Delft, [1930s] (Offsite-box 8, Folder 39)
    - Halve Maen (Half Moon) replica of Henry Hudson's ship, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 40)
    - Historic Richmond Town, Staten Island, New York, 2003 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 41)
    - Historical Society of the Courts of the State of New York program "Before New York There Was New Netherland", 2009 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 42)
    - Holland Society of New York, 1960s (Offsite-box 8, Folder 43)
    - Hudson, Henry, [1909] (Offsite-box 8, Folder 44-a)
    - Illustrations in Holland Dames Record Books, [1907-1933] (Offsite-box 8, Folder 44-b)
      Coeymans Castle, New York, Built before 1700
      Cortelyou House, Long Island, Built 1699
      De Peyster House, New York City, Built before 1695
      De Sille House, Nieuw Utrecht, Built 1657
      Reformed Dutch Church, Beverwyck, Built 1656
      Sip House, New Jersey, Built 1666
      Suydam House, Flushing, Built about 1680
      Van der Heyden Palace, Albany, Built about 1700
      Van Rensselaer House, Albany, Built 1666 (2 versions)
      Van Vechten House, Raritan River, N.J., Built about 1699
      Van Westervelt House, New Hackensack, Built about 1700
      Ver Planck House, on the Hudson, Built about 1700
    - Kingston, New York | City Hall, restoration of plaster lunettes, 2009 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 45)
    - Lent-Riker-Smith Homestead, Queens, New York, undated (Offsite-box 8, Folder 46)
    - Long Island [now Brooklyn] Historical Society, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
    - Loockermans, Govert | Documentation of 1664 deed from Peter Stuyvesant to Loockermans, and photo of frame made from Stuyvesant pear tree wood., 1934 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
      Related Archival Materials
      This 1664 deed (in Dutch) issued by Peter Stuyvesant, as Director General of New Netherland, to Govert Loockermans for land at Canarsie (now in Brooklyn), and its accompanying frame, made of wood from the pear tree Stuyvesant planted at what became the northeast corner of Third Avenue and East 13th Street in Manhattan, were given to the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland by Mrs. William E. (Emma Du Puy) Reed (ca. 1871-1962), a descendant of Loockermans, in 1933. The Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland transfered both to the New-York Historical Society in 2015. They are cataloged as Y-AHMC - Stuyvesant deed (oversize small). For a translation of the deed, see box 1, folder 2, Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland minutes of 2 January 1934.
    - Hendrick I. Lott House, Brooklyn, New York, 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
    - Netherlands illustrations, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
    - Netherlands map, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
      Two copies (one color, one black-and-white) of an undated Rand McNally atlas page showing "Belgium, Netherlands and Western Germany."
    - Netherlands-American Bicentennial Commission, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
    - New Netherland (ship), 1922 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 6)
    - New Netherland Project, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)
    - New-York Historical Society | Gift of books to, 1966 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 8)
    - New-York Historical Society | Stained glass window installation, 1906-1909 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 9)
    - New-York Historical Society | Stained glass window rededication, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, 2007-2013 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 11)
    - NY400 | Henry Hudson 400th anniversary, 2009 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 12)
    - Oudshorn, Holland | church windows, 1904 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 13)
    - Pearl Street tablet | Site of the first church built on Manhattan, 1933 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 14)
    - Photographs | Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland events, 1970-circa 2000 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of the 75th Anniversary Luncheon of the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland, 12 December 1970.
    - Photographs | Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland events, 2011 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 16-a)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore. Letter, 1900 November 22 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 16-b)
      Letter from Theodore Roosevelt, on State of New York Executive Chamber stationery, regretfully declining an invitation to speak before the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland.
    - St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery | St. Mark stained glass window, 2012 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 17)
    - St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery | Peter Stuyvesant stained glass window, installation [1903], 1901-1970 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 18)
    - St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery | Peter Stuyvesant stained glass window, centennial [2003], 2001-2006 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 19)
    - St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery | Peter Stuyvesant stained glass window, rededication, 2009 September 11 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 20)
    - St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery | Peter Stuyvesant stained glass window, restoration & reception (3 folders), 2012 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 21-23)
    - South Street Seaport Museum, 1996-2002 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 24)
    - Stuyvesant, Peter | mother, 2012 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 25)
    - Stuyvesant, Peter | research, 1957, 2001 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 26)
    - Stuyvesant, Peter | statue, 1937 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous material, Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 28)
  - Subseries II.C. Talks & papers delivered before the Society & elsewhere, 1892-2013
    - Suggestions for Writing Papers to Be Read Before the Society [printed pamphlet], undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 29)
    - Bedle, Althea Randolph: "The Influcence of the Holland Dames in the Capitulation of New Netherlands.", undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 30)
    - Bedle, Althea Randolph: "Some of the Old Land Marks in Bergen and Jersey City" [a.k.a. "Old Bergen and Paulus Hook (An historical sketch)"]., 1906 November 6 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 31)
    - Brown, Hulda H. Bergen: "Influence of the Dutch"; address at Colonial Dames Breakfast in San Francisco., 1903 December 5 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 32)
    - Cadena, Mariana Velazquez de la: "MANA-HA-TA and the DUTCH FLAG.", undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 33)
    - Chenoweth, Catharine R. W.: "Paper read on April 6th, 1897, at a Meeting of Daughters of Holland Dames, being a description of medal presented by Mrs. Alexander Crawford Chenoweth.", 1897 April 6 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 34)
    - Chenoweth, Catharine R. W.: "The Inauguration of Queen Wilhelmina.", 1898 September (Offsite-box 9, Folder 35)
    - Johnson, Ruth: "Does America Owe More to the Dutchman, or the Puritan?", undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 36)
      First Prize in Competition of High School pupils for essay on the subject specified, $15 in gold offered by the Colonial Dames. Prize awarded to Ruth Johnson. Reprinted from the High School Journal.
    - Kimmelman, Elbrun: "Windows on Dutch History in New York"; delivered to the Dutch Colonial Society., 2013 April 10 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 37)
    - Poems, prayers, toasts, 1892-1974 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 38)
      Missing Title
      "Hendrick's Prophecy" (1892)
      Beriman (?), Martha Sayre, "The Homecoming of Our Victory Fleet" (1919 December 17)
      Edgar Franklin Romig, "Acrostic for the Fiftieth Anniversary, to the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames" (1945 December 10)
      John P. T. Blake, "A Knickerbocker Toast" (1972-74)
      "Oh Lord... " (n.d.)
    - Randall, Anna J. B.: "Early New Netherland", undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 39)
    - Robinson, Harriet Duer: "A Paper on the Philipse Family", 1897 March 9 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 40)
    - Weart, Clara L.: "Early Settlement of Hudson County, New Jersey.", undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 41)
    - 300th Anniversary Departure of Pilgrims from Holland, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 42)
    - [William the Silent], circa 1900 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 43)
  - Subseries II.D. Artifacts, circa 1898-1990s
    - Bracelet & medals | Queen Wilhelmina, circa 1898-1925 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
      An orange silk or satin jewel box containing objects donated to the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland by Mrs. Alexander Crawford Chenoweth (first Directress General) in 1925:
      Miniature silver bracelet (or crown?), a memento from Queen Wilhelmina's wedding, 1901.
      Medal (white metal) inscribed: "Wilhelmina Koningin der Nederlanden [obverse]"; "Ter Herinnering aan de Kroning Van H. M. Koningin Wilhelmina" [reverse], circa 1898-1925.
      Medal (brown metal, with pendant loop at top) inscribed: "Wilhelmina Koningen der Ned." [obverse], circa 1898-1925.
      Medal (brown metal, in a lapel pin mounting) inscribed: "Wilhelmina Koningen der Nederlanden" [obverse], circa 1898-1925.
    - Medal | Queen Wilhelmina, 1923 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
      Bronze medal commemorating the silver jubilee (i.e., 25th anniversary) of the reign of Queen Wilhelmina of the Netherlands, inscribed "Wilhelmina Koningin der Nederlanden" [obverse] and "MDCCCXCVIII [1898] - MDCCCCXXIII [1923]" [reverse]. Donated by Mrs. Joseph F. Simmons, who in 1923 received this medal as the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland delegate to the jubilee.
    - Medal | Roosevelt, Theodore, 1920 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
      Bronze medal designed by Anna Vaughn Hyatt Huntington and produced by the Medallic Art Company in 1920. Inscribed "Woman's Roosevelt Memorial Association Service" [obverse] and "Theodore Roosevelt / Born October 27, 1858 / Died January 6, 1919" [reverse]. The New-York Historical Society holds another copy of this medal under INV.3562.
    - Ribbon samples and insignia ribbons, 1980s-1990s, undated (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
      Fabric samples for Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland lapel pins.
- Series III. Financial, 1896-2011
  Series III is organized in four subseries:
  Subseries III.A. Treasurer's reports, correspondence, receipts, 1896-2011
  Subseries III.B. Financial Statements & tax returns, 1964-2007
  Subseries III.C. Banking and Investment records, 1938-2000
  Subseries III.D. Miscellaneous financial records, 1898-1995
  This series contains treasurer and accountant reports, bank statements and cancelled checks for the Society of Daughters of Holland Dames, Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Families of New Netherland general and scholarship accounts, investment records, and the Society's IRS 990 form (1987-2007). In later years (1992-2011) the treasurer's reports devolve into informal gatherings of bank statements, receipts, paid bills, and correspondence.
  - Subseries III.A. Treasurer's reports, correspondence, receipts, 1896-2011
    - Treasurer's accounts [bound volume], 1896-1910 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 44)
    - Treasurer's accounts [bound volume], 1925-1930 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 45)
    - Treasurer's accounts [bound volume], 1930-1941 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1932-1938 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer's accounts [bound volume], 1941-1949 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1945-1965 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's accounts, circa 1951-1973 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1966-1976 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer's reports/correspondence, 1992 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 9)
    - Bills paid, 1992 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 10)
    - Treasurer's reports/correspondence (3 folders), 1993 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 11-13)
    - Bills paid, 1993 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 14)
    - Treasurer's reports/correspondence, 1994 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 15)
    - Bills paid, 1996 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 16)
    - Financials (2 folders), 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Expenses, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 19)
    - Finances, 2010 June - 2011 October (Offsite-box 10, Folder 20)
  - Subseries III.B. Financial Statements & tax returns, 1964-2007
    - Auditor's report, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
    - Auditor's report, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    - Auditor's report, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
    - Auditor's report, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
    - Auditor's report, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
    - Auditor's report, 1990 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    - Auditor's report, 1991 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
    - Auditor's report, 1992 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8)
    - Auditor's report, 1999-2007 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 9)
    - Tax exempt status, 1942-1993 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 10)
    - Tax returns (IRS form 990), 1987, 1991 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 11)
    - Tax returns (IRS form 990), 1995-2000 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 12)
    - Tax returns (IRS form 990), 2001-2007 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 13)
  - Subseries III.C. Banking and Investment records, 1938-2000
    - Bankers Trust Company | check stubs, 1938-1943 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bankers Trust Company | check stubs, 1944-1948 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 15)
    - Bankers Trust Company | checks & statements, 1963-1981 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 16)
    - Bankers Trust Company | passbooks: Memorial Fund (2); Educational Endowment (2); Permanent Fund (1), 1959-1982 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    - Bankers Trust Company | miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust | miscellaneous statements & stubs, 1982 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust | check stubs: General Account, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust | check stubs: Scholarship Account, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust | checking, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    - Fidelity Investments, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
    - J. Bush & Co. | General Fund, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
    - J. Bush & Co. | Scholarship Fund, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
    - J. Bush & Co. | appraisals, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 10)
    - Chase Manhattan | Centennial savings account, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
    - Chase Manhattan | Checking account (2 folders), 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12-13)
    - Chase Manhattan | General Fund, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 14)
    - Chase Manhattan | General Fund, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 15)
    - Chase Manhattan | Scholarship Fund, 1994 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 16)
    - Chase Manhattan | Scholarship Fund, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Trust | General and Scholarship funds, 1995-2000 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 18)